<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on Mansfield.ink</title>
    <link>https://mansfield.ink/categories/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on Mansfield.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 06:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansfield.ink/categories/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book 7: Eat That Frog</title>
      <link>https://mansfield.ink/posts/book-7-eat-that-frog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansfield.ink/posts/book-7-eat-that-frog/</guid>
      <description>Eat That Frog! is like reading an extended listicle. The book goes over 21 ways to stop procrastinating and instead work on your goals.
Some of the techniques are geared toward incremental progress, while others are more for someone who has trouble completing a task. I am personally wired to consider a task done when it&amp;rsquo;s 100% completed. Even then, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel that I&amp;rsquo;m ready to complete something until I see a very clear path to the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book 6: The Miracle Morning</title>
      <link>https://mansfield.ink/posts/book-6-miracle-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansfield.ink/posts/book-6-miracle-morning/</guid>
      <description>The Miracle Morning is one of those books you will either love or hate. It&amp;rsquo;s a prescription for a productive start to the day. Whether you take that medicine is up to you.
This book is actually what inspired me to start getting up early. I realized I spent a lot of time after my kids went to bed just watching videos and sometimes playing games. I&amp;rsquo;d stay up until after midnight and wake up just barely on time to get my kids to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book 4: Who Not How</title>
      <link>https://mansfield.ink/posts/book-4-who-not-how/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 06:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansfield.ink/posts/book-4-who-not-how/</guid>
      <description>Who Not How by Dan Sullivan and Dr. Benjamin Hardy flips the typical script upside down. Instead of concentrating on how to solve a problem yourself, you should instead look for people who can solve that problem for you. By delegating rather than doing, you can free your time to do higher level, higher value tasks.
This book revisits the same concept of $10,000 per hour work that we saw in Virtual Freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
